Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
You know, you and me, we're family, right?
Yeah, of course.
Not by blood or anything, though.
Right.
But we're closer than a lot of people who are related by blood, aren't we?
I guess so. Why, what's up?
I was thinking. You and me, we don't have any real relatives, but we've got a lot of great friends.
What I think is we should take the friends we have now and the ones we'll meet later and make them our family.
We're almost there now. It should be just through this hallway.
Isn't that simply marvelous?
Some dungeon that was. Not much to it at all.
So what's your plan for getting past this?
It doesn't appear as if the Black Bulls have managed to find it yet.
Of course they haven't. Despite their bluster, they never stood a chance of beating us here.
You're probably right.
Mimosa! Such a keen monosense, but she never saw it coming.
This is no trap magic. So, what is it?
Who goes there?
You're in my way.
Now move. See what you really need.
Our friends you know you can count on.
Well, sorry about this, but I've got things to do.
You know how it is.
Win.
Keep on winning, Fluck.
Hold on.
It's been too long.
Since things have gotten this interesting.
Oh yeah!
Let's do this!
Time to fight!
So much potential.
I'm almost sorry to extinguish it.
Oh shit.
Look!
Why can't you just do what I ask?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Stop smiling like that!
Get mad!
Cry!
Do something normal!
Why were you born a defective freak?
No way!
Whoa!
I can't believe this.
An ordinary citizen defeated a noble?
It's never happened in all the time our schools held this tournament.
Regular people don't win against nobles.
Oh man, I've been giving that kid a hard time too.
What if he decides to get me back?
It's so creepy the way he smiles all the time.
Don't go near that guy unless you want a beating.
What a freak.
You actually beat a noble using your magic.
Holak!
That's fantastic!
Who knew you would turn out to be so powerful?
Most people like us don't stand a chance against the nobles.
But obviously you're special.
You're special.
You're a hero, you're a hero, you're a hero.
I'm a hero, and I'm in the right now.
I'm in the right now.
Oh man, I've been giving that kid a hard time too.
What if he decides to get me back?
It's so creepy the way he smiles all the time.
Don't go near that guy unless you want a beating.
What a freak.
You actually beat a noble using your magic.
Holak, that's fantastic!
Who knew you would turn out to be so powerful?
Most people like us don't stand a chance against the nobles.
but obviously you're special and you'll win again won't you use that power of yours to win
and win and keep on winning in this world nobody's going to help you you have to help yourself
use the power only you possess i'll do it mom if it'll make you happy
interesting boy in spite of my magic he's only gotten faster and sharper
win i'm going to keep on winning that's what my power is for
terribly sorry i'm afraid that i can't afford to lose either
smoke creation magic binding cross prison
this smoke is solid i can't move oh dear that particular spell uses so much magic power
i'd hoped i would be able to avoid casting it i'm downright exhausted now but at least you won't
be hopping around anymore youngster you're dealt with and now it's time to see how my
own youngster is faring honestly i have such difficulty getting through to him sometimes
maybe it's the generation gap
plant recovery magic
dream healing flower cradle
i'm so sorry sir i should have sensed something i'm the group's healer
what use will i be to you now don't worry about that mimosa you only need to focus on your own recovery
that insignia is he a mage from the wretched diamond kingdom
you there attacking from behind what kind of warrior would do such a thing
i don't understand what you're asking who are you you are merely pebbles destined to fall by the wayside
i don't know what you're talking about
let's go yuno back me up right when we get done with this barbarian he won't
soon forget the power of clover kingdom's golden dawn
now we're talking no hidden trap spells along this path
the mana just keeps getting thicker is that really the treasure hall up ahead
what's up all this magic power there's a battle somewhere that's where luck went
who's he fighting likely someone from the diamond kingdom they're here then we should go help luck
should we luck likes fighting we could leave it to him couldn't we and keep going
if there are mages from the diamond kingdom here you can bet they'll be headed for the treasure hall
and protecting it is supposed to be our priority this mission has to be carried out swiftly and
thoroughly i want to keep those diamond guys paws off the good stuff if we don't hurry the golden dawn
will get the credit
when i have to keep on winning with my own power
huh i'm guessing something more than smoke is tying you in nuts
i almost had it where did it go
wait i can't remember what am i looking for again
there's so much strength behind his attacks and he's not even using a grimoire
no sign of his magic power decreasing either
if this keeps up
right you know i'll stay here and hold him off go on ahead to the treasure hall
he's extremely strong are you sure you can handle him without backup stop questioning me and do as i say
we're out of options i don't like leaving this task in the hands of a commoner
but for the good of our kingdom we will complete our mission
it's about time you brat
no
here boy i can take all your worries away
you know you and me we're family right
we're closer than a lot of people who are related by blood
another spirited fellow come to join us i see
i guess so why what's up what are you doing you imbecile i was thinking well hello there and who are you
who am i you and me we don't have any real relatives but we've got a lot of great friends
the mission needs to be your priority right now we should take the friends we have now and the ones
we'll meet later and make them our family no sir
you are my friend
right you know i'll stay here and hold them off go on ahead to the treasure hall
it's about time you brat
here boy i can take all your worries away
what were you thinking coming back here you imbecile we have a mission to complete and that means
getting to the treasure hall even if you must go alone
first we defeat him then we go to the hall together
you're taking us on now you ready oh your friends are coming out to play too how delightful
from what they say sounds like she just up and died she did seem to be under a lot of stress
left your kid behind too poor thing must be heartbroken
well i don't know about that he's a strange one his mother's dead and he's smiling
he's mine
luck wait he's my prey
win i will win and dedicate my victory to you mom
i'll take him on alone stay back
i don't need friends to help me win i'll use the power only i possess please luck let us help
i have to do it by myself or i'll never earn my mom's acceptance
fine have it your way
is that all this really isn't the time to hold back you know
i'll do it i'll win i have to
i need her to accept me or i'll be all alone
you go ahead and do what you gotta do look but so will i got it i have to beat him on my own
sorry but that just isn't happening
i'm not done
in some way i don't know what you think of me and it doesn't matter
do whatever you want i was trying not to notice
but you're my friend you're our friend so let us help yeah
trying not to see that even i have friends who i can count on
i'm sorry mom it turns out i'm not alone after all
you're right it does sound a lot more fun to fight together sure does
well this isn't a good turn of events
if that's how it's going to be i suppose it's time to get serious
it's time to go this ends now what are you
it's time to get out of our way diamond mage
the golden dawn will reach the hall first
yeah
i'm cutting and cutting and cutting but it's just not cutting it here
dizzy this place is filling up with smoke i'll wind up suffocating at this rate
our only chance is to defeat the spellcaster in fast
i can sense his magic power so i have a good idea of where he might be
if we attack he'll most likely dodge it what do i know about his fighting style so far
when he's inside the smoke he can move really fast and he can pick up on magic power quickly too
our best shot is to find a way to blindside him but how when he can sense our magic
this spell is a very high power
i may not be young like you three but i can do this all day
i can see my opponents
don't get any foolish ideas i can sense your magic power so sneak attacks aren't going to work on me
whoa
whoa there
wow rapid fire getting desperate are we
i'm afraid you won't be able to hit me like that it won't clear the smoke either
all you're doing now is wasting your power
i suppose it all comes down to experience i've likely been in more battles than all of you combined
first i cornered him then using every drop of my magic and in a fraction of a second so he wouldn't
notice up you go
and asta with no magic power to give him away
attack
that went really well
you know you were right earlier teamwork is vital
what how is that possible
be gone
you
me
To go
消えそうな光でも
闇を照らす力が
繋がって時の流れを変える
色褪せない場所に
終わらない夢を掴むため
進むべき道があるなら
Do you wanna drive? Do you wanna drive?
このままどこまででも
僕の命が終わるまで
どんな痛みも受け入れよう
We can drive down! We can drive down!
たとえ明日が見えなくても
声にならない想いを抱いて
叫び続ける in my heart
Clover Clips
Family
So, you know, is it true that when you make new friends
you treasure them like you would your own family?
What a lovely idea! That sounds so wonderful!
Yeah
Family, so does it look a little something like this?
Hey, Big Brother Klaus
Oh, that tickles
Little brother, you know
I got something special for you
My own glasses!
Wow, you're the best!
Thank you, brother
Yeah, no way
This guy's powerful, alright
But I can't let myself be defeated now
Not if I'm going to become the Wizard King
Black Clover
Page 17
Destroyer
My magic is never giving up!
Never giving up!